Hello

I'm Williams Alex

Full-Stack Software Engineer

+234 7012714644

williamsalexir@gmail.com

Github link

Linkedin

Bio

I'm a Software engineer with over 4 and half years of working experience.

I derive joy in performing my duties with the technologies I've used throughout my working experience.

I also love to learn new technologies and expand my knowledge as a software engineer.

Solving problems and creating new ideas and inventions is like an everyday task for me, it keeps me going.

Experience

Mar 2023 - Present | Uburu Health · Full-time

Software Engineer

Made modifications and upgraded the company's website/application.

Jul 2021 - Present | Intelligent Innovations Co. · Full-time

Software Engineer

- Built the company's website using Next js.
- Built various email templates using vanilla Html and Css technologies
- Built an e-learning or edu tech platform using both Nuxt js and Next/Nx, you can learn various skills from this platform, for more head on to https://skillpaddy.com
- Made modifications and upgraded a financial platform where you can basically apply for loans.
- Modified and built a job application platform, this forum allows users to be able to apply and create jobs.

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022 | TopUp Mama · Contract

Software Engineer

- Built user interface for the company's sales dashboard
- Learn't tailwind css and chakra ui

Software Engineer

- Built a full stack application that allows users to be able to conduct voting actions for beauty contests.
- Learnt and wrote unit test for the application, i wrote the test using jest
- Deployed the application on both development and production environments

Feb 2020 - May 2021 | Diamond Acre Software · Full-time

Software Engineer

- Created user interface for the companies website, the technologies used were vanilla Html5, Css3 and JavaScript.
- Created mobile interfaces which used Vue.js and Quiser library to render its UI as a cross platform mobile application.
- Made modifications to one of the company's big products using React js.
- Created a full stack quiz application, the technologies used was Vue, the Quiser library, Node js/Express framework and MongoDB database
- Learned about Nginx technology

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020 · Green Mouse Technologies · Full-time

Software Engineer and Tutor

- Created user interfaces for various websites/applications with technologies like Html5, Css3, Javascript and Bootstrap.
- Made more use of CSS3 animations and transitions on the some of the company's application
- Created mock ups for the company's products.
- Learnt a bit of PHP
- Tutored students who needed to learn about web development and tech in general

Skills

SCSS

Tailwind CSS

JavaScript

TypeScript

React

Vue

Next

Nuxt

Node/Express

MongoDB

Education

2017

Gateway polytechnic Saapade, Ogun State Nigeria.

HND, Computer Science.